{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776096664","data":{"timestamp":" 946776096664"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_90_96-90-76"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 90"," userResponse":" 96"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776105915","data":{"timestamp":" 946776105915"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_90_96-90-76"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 90"," userResponse":" 76"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776113722","data":{"timestamp":" 946776113722"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_90_96-90-76"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 90"," userResponse":" 90"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776121390","data":{"timestamp":" 946776121390"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_75_91-75-108"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 75"," userResponse":" 91"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776129782","data":{"timestamp":" 946776129782"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_75_91-75-108"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 75"," userResponse":" 75"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776142408","data":{"timestamp":" 946776142408"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-50-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 50"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776149828","data":{"timestamp":" 946776149827"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-50-92"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776159435","data":{"timestamp":" 946776159435"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_60_59-60-76"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 60"," userResponse":" 60"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946776223382","data":{"timestamp":" 946776223382"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_54_84-54-103"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 54"," userResponse":" 54"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780222401","data":{"timestamp":" 946780222401"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_54_84-54-103"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780228307","data":{"timestamp":" 946780228307"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" a820ad59-5c82-40f6-9ae2-53ae545d98d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_54_84-54-103"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780236875","data":{"timestamp":" 946780236875"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780237099","data":{"timestamp":" 946780237099"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780238061","data":{"timestamp":" 946780238061"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780238756","data":{"timestamp":" 946780238756"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780238839","data":{"timestamp":" 946780238839"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780247091","data":{"timestamp":" 946780247090"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" cd88e2c6-4a93-42f7-85f4-cfc59060ebf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780288146","data":{"timestamp":" 946780288146"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" 2a5227a9-c75d-43b6-8c1f-05c959545696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_57_57-67-100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 57"," userResponse":" 57"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780288632","data":{"timestamp":" 946780288631"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000102_042113"," gameId":" 2a5227a9-c75d-43b6-8c1f-05c959545696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL1.decr.56"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_57_57-67-100"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}